YVETTE JOHNSON-RODGERS

Albuquerque, New Mexico | (505) 859-6496 <u>yvette@yvette.io</u> | <u>www.yvette.io</u> | <u>Github: yvejr</u> <u>LinkedIn: Yvette Johnson-Rodgers</u>

SUMMARY

After working closely with technology for the last ten years, I decided to go further into the digital world by actually creating apps and web pages for other people to use. I started by teaching myself HTML and CSS, and really enjoyed the combination of using a concrete computer language to accomplish a creative goal in the form of live, interactive content. I decided to make this a career change and joined Deep Dive Coding, a 10 week long intensive coding bootcamp. I look forward to developing for a local Albuquerque tech company, where I can bring my positive attitude and client first mindset.

HIGHLIGHTED SKILLS

Tech Skills: Angular, Bootstrap, CSS3, HTML5, Javascript, jQuery, MySQL, PHP and PHPUnit; familiarity with Windows: XP, Vista, 7, 8, 8.1; iOS, Android; Microsoft Office, G Suite, Adobe PS LightRoom; knowledge of design patterns; experience with command line scripting, hardware, software, and network troubleshooting

People Skills: Leadership, management, public speaking, training, developmental coaching, customer service, business support, technical support

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES

Deep Dive Coding Fullstack Bootcamp Certificate - 400 hours of immersive study	June 2018
he University of New Mexico Albuquerque, NM	2007-2014
Bachelor of Arts in Communication, focus in Interpersonal Communication	
Minor in Psychology	
Tech Skills Network+ Class	June 2016

COMPTIA A+ Certification May 2010
Hardware and Service Technician

RECENT EXPERIENCE

Verizon 2008-2018

Management

• Participated in a year long leadership development program, honing my leadership skills and practicing them as center and team support and employee engagement programs.

- Identified needs for supplemental training, developed and delivered them to large groups.
- Six months in an active leadership role as a Supervisor, managing two teams total, of 10 people and 15 people respectively.

Trainer and Coach

- Provided development, training, and on the job support for 9 teams of agents new to the Tech Support role.
- Updated and later re-created new materials for daily and weekly focus for the 6 week program.

Tech Support

- Supported customer base in all mobile operating systems, computers using the cellular network, and voice services for all phones.
- Handled customer concerns while balancing the needs of the business such as average handle time, financial credits, and sales goals.

COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT

Reading Works, Inc. 2014 - Present

Adult Tutor for Literacy and High School Equivalency Exam

Albuquerque MeetUp Groups

Girl Develop It

Deep Dive Coding